Add video to Hotspot
将视频添加到热点
First, go to the main menu and click “Media Library”
首先，进入主菜单，点击“Media Library”
Click “Video files”
点击“Video files”
Add a video file from computer to library
从计算机中向库中添加视频文件
Now return to CTA menu, and create a CTA area
现在返回CTA菜单，创建一个CTA区域
Click “Play Video” on the left menu
在左侧菜单点击“Play Video”
Enter a Title name and select “Add from Media Library”
输入标题名称，选择“Add from Media Library”
Add the video file you just added
添加刚刚添加的视频文件
You can also directly upload the video from your computer
您还可以直接从计算机上传视频
Okay, now let's try the first display method: “Screen Overlay”
好的，现在让我们尝试第一种显示方法：“Screen Overlay”
Set the window size and position Let's start by placing the “anchor point” at the top left
设置窗口大小和位置，首先将“anchor point”放置在左上角
Now, preview
现在，预览
You can see the 360 image is on the right, occupying 75% of the screen
您可以看到视频在右侧，占据了屏幕的75%
Let's go back and change to full screen
让我们返回并切换到全屏模式
Click to confirm and Preview
点击确认并预览
Now you can see when you click the hotspot, the video will play in full screen
现在您可以看到当您点击热点时，视频将全屏播放
Now let’s try the second method: “Embed in block center”
现在让我们尝试第二种方法：“Embed in block center”
Click to confirm and Preview
点击确认并预览
You can see the video is strictly limited to the hotspot area
您可以看到视频严格限制在热点区域内
Now, let's try the third method: “Preset Display Window”
现在，让我们尝试第三种方法：“Preset Display Window”
First, create a new hotspot area and place it on the left
首先，创建一个新的热点区域，放置在左侧
Set it as a “Display Window”
将其设置为“Display Window”
Enter a name
输入名称
Select the hotspot area press “Play Video” on left and choose “Preset Display Window“ on right
在左侧点击“Play Video”，在右侧选择“Preset Display Window”
Select the display window name you just added
选择您刚刚添加的显示窗口名称
The video is shown in the display window you created
视频显示在您创建的显示窗口中
Finally, let's try the last display method: “Embed Within Block Area”
最后，让我们尝试最后一种显示方法：“Embed Within Block Area”
Select “Embed Within Block Area” and define the window size and anchor point
选择“Embed Within Block Area”，定义窗口大小和“anchor point”
This operation is similar to the previously mentioned “Screen Overlay”
这个操作类似于前面提到的“Screen Overlay”
The difference with 'Screen Overlay' is that the window is only shown within its own block area
与'Screen Overlay'的不同之处在于，窗口仅显示在其自身的块区域内
Now let's resize and change the “anchor point”
现在让我们调整大小并更改“anchor point”
You can see the window has changed its position and size, but it still remains within the boundaries of its block
您可以看到窗口已经改变了位置和大小，但仍保持在其块的边界内